Hats
	A Gosu bling-bling hat. The Korean word "Gosu" means "Super-badass" in the gaming world. The player unlocks this hat after beating the game on the hardest setting, so it has to look super sexy. Use the Korean characters for Gosu (고수) done out in gold and diamonds. see http://www.google.com/imgres?q=bling+bling&um=1&hl=en&safe=off&sa=N&biw=1440&bih=809&tbm=isch&tbnid=smcZ6IeveuRXxM:&imgrefurl=http://www.mtv.com/photos/a-flash-of-bling-bling-hip-hoppers-and-their-crown-jewels/1507792/1774079/photo.jhtml&docid=-FSNiuysPDekRM&w=500&h=365&ei=5rpvTp2tE9LTgQfJw72NBQ&zoom=1&iact=hc&vpx=177&vpy=185&dur=1731&hovh=192&hovw=263&tx=130&ty=114&page=1&tbnh=132&tbnw=176&start=0&ndsp=32&ved=1t:429,r:0,s:0 
	Giant brain (replaces stickman head)
	Mario hat (plus a mustache?)
	Super Meat Boy hat ( tribute to http://supermeatboy.com/ )
	Knight's helmet (tribute to http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Ghouls'n_Ghosts )

Princess in a bubble

Hero icon, in a bubble. Cake, rainbow cake, pill, double jump?, normal? just use smaller normal hero icon?
Game icon, multiple variants, BIG SIZES

Category menu
	Arcade: Playing an arcade game (Playing cloudberrying kingdom!)(or Diib's Dilemna? Mario?)
	Awardments: In a hat room. Hat rack?
	Shop: At a street vendor
	Hero Rush: ???
	Hero Rush 2: ???
	Maybe: Freeplay, Campaign
	(Send current pictures)

Help!
The End (brought in by blobs)

Beam of light

Dead stickman, dead blob (Send current score screen)

-------------
Super crying berry, anime style, tears flying off parabolically
Stickman hugging princess in a bubble, portrait style
Super happy berry, splash screen size
Mooning cloudberry





sounds:
Beam of light aural sounds, + turn on stage-light sound
T-Rex
Rain
Blobs flapping (medium and intense, transition? [drop castle phase change])
Closing black circle
Crowd cheers (think cosmo from gremlins, slightly pigeon-esque whrrreeerrrrrr!)
Single berry cheer
Lightning
Boss explode, Pre-boss explode?










Bling-BlingHooray college! If I could go back to college and do it all over again... ah, hell, I'd probably still drink just as much. Are you majoring in art?

Alright, so, the game is mostly done at this point, we're just putting some finishing touches on, and trying to figure out a plot maybe =D Here's the basic break down of what we need art-wise:

1) Hats!

We've got a whole achievement system now where the player can earn hats for doing cool things. So, we need cool looking hats to reward the player (the current hats are cool, but we've only got a few). We'll probably shoot for 10 to 20 hats, but the important hats are given for beating the game on different difficulties, they are

	Giant brain (replaces stickman head)
	Mario hat (plus a mustache?)
	Super Meat Boy hat ( tribute to http://supermeatboy.com/ )
	Knight's helmet (tribute to http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Ghouls'n_Ghosts )

	And finally, a Gosu Bling-Bling hat. What the hell is a Gosu Bling-Bling hat you may ask. The Korean word "Gosu" means "Super-badass" in the gaming world http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gosu. The player unlocks this hat after beating the game on the hardest setting, so it has to look super sexy. Use the Korean characters for Gosu (고수) done out in huge gold and diamonds studded characters, see Bling-Bling. Maybe the Korean characters are stuck to a sweat band wrapped around the stickman's head. A big fluffy sweat band.

2) Princess in a bubble

See the attached image "Princess_In_A_Bubble" for what we currently are using (which sucks). The basic plot of the game is the princess is kidnapped by a horde of flying blobs, and they keep her in a bubble. The blobs turn into a massive blob man for the final boss, see the attached image "Boss". Anyway, a better Princess-in-a-bubble would be great. Maybe she looks concerned, or has her hands pressed against the bubble. A few variants here would be nice, as it's a central object in the game.

3) Category Menu

Once you start the game you're presented with lots of different actual games to play. You can play the story mode (called "Classic"), or various other arcade style games. See the attached image "Menu_Story". Each item on the menu has an associated picture that appears on the right hand side. We like some of these pictures, some of them not so much. Right now the picture for classic ("Menu_Story") and for escalation ("Arcade_Escalation") are our favorites, but the other's are weaker, so we're looking to revamp them. Use the ones we like as a basis for the style we are going for. We have a few ideas here:

	Awardments: This item on the menu is where the player goes to see all of the hats they've unlocked. The picture could be a coat rack or closet filled with hats. Or maybe just piles of hats.

	Hat Shop: In addition to earning hats the player can buy hats with coins they pick up. The picture could be a Cloudberry Person running a little outdoor street shop selling hats.

	Arcade ("Menu_Arcade"): this item leads to all the arcade games, so we figure the picture should be of a Cloudberry Person playing an old school arcade game. The game he's playing should either be "Cloudberry Kingdom", or "Stickman Bob", which is our private name for the stickman hero.

	Hero Rush ("Arcade_HeroRush"): I'm happy with this one, but TJ hates it, so let's make it low priority. The idea we have though is this. One of the heroes you can play as is called "Wheelie", where you are strapped to a big wooden wheel, see image "HeroImage_Wheel". You roll around to get places. Anyway, for the picture we'd like a Wheelie stickman wheeling toward an open door, with all the other hero apparel scattered around him. This can have some perspective to the drawing, or not, whatever looks good.

	Hero Rush 2: Also happy with this, but TJ hates it. Low priority unless you're inspired. I was thinking having a double jump hero ("HeroImage_DoubleJump") jumping up in the air over a bunch of dead heroes, or obstacles, or something.

	Freeplay: I really like this one, TJ also hates it. Low priority unless you're inspired.
